he's just quickly talking about the
alchemy principle that we were talking
about this morning of these two systems
have you have you achieved what we're
calling alchemy or the multiplication of
elements within the water in either one
of these are both in these two systems
we do that system I don't want that to
happen
I don't want multi I don't want minerals
or elements to multiply it because
there's no way for the real way for them
to get out
this system is a standalone system I
have systems like that that have been
running for years so we'll want to talk
about when you don't want it what to do
to prevent it right well what you do to
prevent it
what you do to prevent it is use
distilled water and sodium hydroxide and
a few little catalysts you imbibe my
electric water throw that in there that
can eliminate what we call co2 soaking
co2 soaking is when your is when your
your hydrogen device runs down and the
plates are covered with a co2 layer you
start to see a black film developing and
sometimes there are other colors and
that actually starts to start to reduce
your efficiency by using the electric
water and some of the the catalysts that
we've created with using the gold and
the platinum and such you completely
eliminate co2 soaking this unit runs
better after six months than it does
when it's brand-new okay because it runs
better the longer it goes unlike unlike
most systems which suffer from co2
soaking and a couple of other ailments
that start to clog up their plates so
that's that's what you use frequencies
for usually is to is to strip that off
but I don't like the use of frequencies
so much as I like these catalysts and so
that that for a very simple system with
very minimal catalysts or maintenance
that's quite a remarkable because never
the catalyst never really where
because we have the reservoirs that feed
the catalyst back to the machine okay so
the catalyst never really wears out the
catalyst is always being recycled how
often are you measuring the ratio or the
concentration once I put it in there
don't usually it doesn't really well
that's one thing that I will talk about
when we start multiplying the minerals
is that when you use heavy acids or
heavy alkalis that for some reason that
actually inhibits the process of
multiplication and what we want to do
over here so and by the way if other
people in the audience have questions
that you want to ask you think got to be
brought up at any point feel free so
like I said this is the system this is
the basic system and this type of system
that we can run for for incredible
amounts of time I put them on semi
trucks that put them on oil wells I put
them on standalone generators that type
of thing because they're they're
bomb-proof and they're they're very very
sturdy so I like the this is what we
call this is a dry cell this will you'll
see is a wet cell and this is a hybrid
it's got plates that are pressed
together with a spacer in between and so
there's not a lot of room for water to
get or there's not a lot of ease of
communication for water in there but it
slowly seeps and fills up all the cell's
so that's kind of a hybrid system it's
lined with teflon inside there to make
certain that it's very very heat
resistant oh there's one thing I really
want to stress if you're building a
hydrogen device hydrogen boils at 100
are some a 210 degree our water boils at
210 degrees inside of a hydrogen device
water boils at 140 degrees okay it's a
completely different environment inside
there so if you're if your device is
running hotter than 140 150 degrees
you're actually boiling
creating Steve and that's very dangerous
especially for a ninja not some dangers
for torch that's okay but for an engine
that's really bad so be aware of that
that's why these also service as safety
systems to keep any any steam from
getting into the engine so that's that's
a little preparatory part remember two
point three five volts per cell
one quarter amp per square inch and that
is a pretty good round number two to
remember as you're as you're building
your devices where did you come up with
those numbers those those I studied a
long time with Bob boyce and I read a
huge amount by by George Wiseman and Yul
Brown and those were the numbers that I
found fit that the criteria the best and
they've proven out over and over again
if you if you go over current you'll
crystallize your plates and stop
producing gas you may get a lot of gas
it won't be great gas and over time the
plates will stop producing so your so
your efficiency on your hydrogen device
will go down if you go over voltage your
plates will start falling apart oh we
bought so many devices we bought round
devices and my family and I and we
played with with a lot of different
devices and we found every single which
way to fail and we've we got a tube
device they're using baking soda as the
catalyst we ran that thing like they
said we could but at a peak output we
ran it for about four or five maybe a
week but I think in about four or five
days pull that thing apart it fell in
half because the plates have just eaten
themselves to death
baking soda not a good way to go in my
opinion
I don't know anybody else maybe somebody
else has a fantastic experience with it
with the long term and harsh conditions
this seems to be the best way to go
moving right along
one of my one of my fields of research
is health and longevity as as we've
already mentioned with the with the
different waters of my family and I've
created and so I wanted to find a way to
deliver beneficial elements and such to
the body and more quickly and
effectively and I turned to my hydrogen
research because you'll Brown when he
was doing his work he could send divers
down supplied with a supply of Browns
gas he could send divers down twice as
deep and come up two or three times as
fast as a regular diver because the
hydrogen and oxygen was was going into
the cells the oxygen was was oxen the
needed oxygen to the tissues and then
the oxygen hydrogen was recombining as
water and not producing any toxic gases
in the body so they can come up faster
without any bends so and then there were
several gentlemen as a matter of fact
some of the people here have actually
done work with healing and and curing of
chronic disease are working with at
least relieving chronic diseases using
Browns gas and I've read many of these
accounts and so it's very very excited
so I study then created the device that
allows me to use no sodium hydroxide of
all and and instead use just the either
the etheric elements or the Ormus
elements that I work with and breathe
those substances and that's what this
this started this turned out to be and
you put you put water in with it with a
little reservoir the gas comes out and
you can breathe that directly and excuse
me oh boy howdy it's good stuff gets rid
of headaches there's talk of actually
people putting plastic bags over
sprained wrists and such and healing the
healing the injuries even even stroke
victims so there's a lot of there's a
lot we can go and go pretty deep into
that but we don't that's this is not the
forum but what I noticed was when I
added an alchemical fluid to this this
system right here the alchemical fluid
that was very very difficult to make and
took a long time to produce suddenly was
multiplying it got thicker and darker in
the in the in the reservoir I said wait
a minute
that shouldn't be happening I've worked
for years to try and figure out a faster
way to make this so when I analyzed it I
realized oh look there's it's actually
concentrating it's actually more
concentrated than when I started so at
that point I remembered some experiments
that we're done and realized that it's
possible that I was actually multiplying
chemical compounds and multiplying
elements so should I tell that story or
should we just go let's just go on with
this here yeah we they can go to part
one because we talked about that in part
one didn't we yes that's why we're good
okay okay so let me show you what I did
here now you're gonna what you actually
see here is a violation of the rules
that I already laid down but that's
because we're not using sodium hydroxide
we're using less plates and we actually
end up giving it a little bit more we
actually end up giving it a little bit
more voltage what you see here is a
conventional I know it's very dirty but
but that's good good elements that you
see in there i drained out most of it
you can see some of the red red stuff
down there excuse me this was all
completely clear when I started and it's
a it's a system that uses no sodium
hydroxide because as I said sending
hydroxide interferes with the
interferes with the process and and I
know people seeing the video are saying
well look at that red stuff he's
disintegrating plates I'm not
disintegrating plates I have measured
all of these things and with micrometers
and I'm not disintegrating the plates at
all I'm actually multiplying and
dropping out elements and so what you
see here is essentially this system
a little bit different voltage current
ratios this is my first system that I
ran off of a solar panel literally what
you're seeing here this device generates
about 20 litres an hour using 20 20
liters of hydrogen an hour using only a
little $45 solar panel from Harbor
Freight okay how many square feet is it
uh probably about four and a half five
okay four nine five square feet
it's not even they're big they're big
powerful one this is just an experiment
I did and I haven't measured the output
from when I hooked it up to the big big
panels but the the little solar panel is
generating about 20 litres an hour so
about a third of the leader a minute
and so we've got here we have a fuel
that we can use to cook our food heat
our houses it's being generated by the
Sun and at the same time it's creating a
byproduct of an element of gold and so
that's the the basic the basics of it
now what you have to do you can't see it
in there very well so what I'm going to
do is I'm going to hold this here
essentially you put together a set of
stainless steel plates with spacers here
I use an o-ring or actually it's a quad
ring it gives me twice as much surface
area of contact than an o-ring but
that's another story here I use an
o-ring in here I use a strip here and a
strip here and allow free communication
of water down and up so that that way
the minerals and elements that are
multiplied can fall down and the gas
from the height of the hydrogen and
oxygen gas can rise and so there's so
it's completely unobstructed in this
system it's contained so that of course
it doesn't leak and the gas comes out
the top so that's basically what I have
inside there what's up it is a wet cell
this is what is considered a wet cell
system we're not looking for - here you
said there's basically a long
each side could you point out where
those are it looks like you have a
little spacers right about there and
right about there yeah there's there's
some spacers right about there and once
again I violated the rules I didn't go
1/8 inch so spacing
I literally just used a time solution I
used SIP ties and use those spacers
because they're a little bit less than
1/16 of an inch
see in this system we're putting our
energy into making the the elements and
we're not we're not concerned about
super high efficiency like with my
hydrogen device so we can play with some
of the variables
yes I have less neutrals so as he said
more heat is generated and more there's
a little bit different current ratios so
in this one here's the numbers I've got
a positive and a negative plate and one
two three four four neutrals so one two
three four five cells five cells on each
side so for a total of 10 cells and I
run about 16 volts for 4 3 amps maximum
into here with a power supply and what
that does is that that drops out such a
huge amount of elements like I said all
the water was completely clear when I
started and the plates are not
disintegrating I take this apart
routinely and well every month every
couple weeks or so
measure the plates I'm not
disintegrating the plates I'm actually
dropping out elements out of the water
and your elements to multiply it because
there's no way for real way for them to
get out
this system is a standalone system I
have systems like that that have been
running for years so we'll want to talk
about when you don't want it what to do
to prevent it right well what you do to
prevent it what you do to prevent it is
use distilled water and sodium hydroxide
and a few little catalyst you imbibe my
electric water throw that in there that
can eliminate what we conscious I like
these and catalysts and so that that for
a very simple system with very minimal
catalysts or maintenance that's quite a
remarkable because never the catalyst
never really wears out because we have
the reservoirs that feed the catalyst
back to the machine okay so the catalyst
never really wears out the catalyst is
always being recycled how often are you
you just quickly talking about the
alchemy principle that we were talking
about this morning of these two systems
have you have you achieved what we're
calling alchemy or the multiplication of
elements within the water in either one
of these are both in these two systems
we do that system I don't want that to
happen
I don't want multi I don't want mineral
so all co2 soaking co2 soaking is when
you're is when you're your hydrogen
device runs down and the plates are
covered with a co2 layer you start to
see a black film developing and
sometimes there are other colors and
that actually starts to start to reduce
your efficiency by using the electric
water and some of the the catalysts that
we've created with using the gold and
the platinum and such you completely
eliminate co2 soaking this unit runs
better after six months than it does
when it's brand-new okay because it runs
better the longer it goes unlike unlike
most systems which suffer from co2
soaking and a couple of other ailments
that start to clog up their plates so
that's that's what you use frequencies
for usually is to is to strip that off
but I don't like the use of frequencies
some